<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="about_title">Threema Work for Android</string>
	<string name="enter_serial_body">Please enter the credentials provided by your company or organization</string>
	<string name="serial_required_want_exit">License is invalid. Would you like to try again or quit Threema?</string>
	<string name="checking_serial">Checking credentials</string>
	<string name="username_hint">Username</string>
	<string name="new_wizard_works_like_phone_number">Your Threema ID works just like a phone number.\nYour contacts can reach you through this ID.</string>
	<string name="new_wizard_nickname_explain">Your contacts will see your nickname in their notifications.</string>
	<string name="new_wizard_help_your_friends_find_you">Help your contacts find you!</string>
	<string name="new_wizard_find_friends">Find your contacts on Threema Work</string>
	<string name="new_wizard_sync_contacts_explain">Switch on to see which of your contacts is already using Threema or Threema Work.</string>
	<string name="new_wizard_anonymous_confirm">You have entered neither a mobile number nor an email address to link to your Threema ID. You will not appear on contact lists. Do you really want to use Threema Work anonymously?</string>
	<string name="new_wizard_setup_threema">Set up Threema Work</string>
	<string name="new_wizard_welcome">Welcome to Threema Work!</string>
	<string name="new_wizard_info_fingerprint">By moving your finger, you create random data (called entropy) that is used to generate
		the keypair associated with your new unique Threema ID. The keypair consists of a <b>public key</b> that is distributed to
		your contacts and a <b>private key</b> that is safely stored on your phone. Your contacts will encrypt messages to you with
		your public key. Only the owner of the private key and nobody else is able to decrypt these messages.
	</string>
	<string name="new_wizard_info_link">By providing your phone number and email address, Threema Work can help your contacts
		find you automatically if they have you in their phone’s address book. The data will be stored in a
		one-way encrypted (hashed) form on our server. You can simply skip this step, if you would like to use Threema Work
		anonymously.
	</string>
	<string name="threema_contact">Threema Work Contact</string>
	<string name="menu_about">About Threema Work</string>
	<string name="list_theme_light">Light</string>
	<string name="list_theme_dark">Dark (default)</string>
	<string name="private_threema_download"><![CDATA[If you are a private user, please <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=ch.threema.app">tap here</a> to download Threema.]]></string>
	<string name="directory_search">Search in the directory</string>
	<string name="directory_title">Company directory</string>
	<string name="directory_empty_view_text">No entries found\n\nPlease enter at least 3 characters of a name to begin searching in your company\'s directory of Threema users</string>
</resources>
